In the year 850, the Colossal Titan
reappeared and demolished another wall.
Once again, humanity allowed
the Titans to further their advance.
One after another,
soldiers fell to the Titans.
And then...
Eren!
Hurry!
Eren fell prey to a Titan too.
Man, Mikasa's incredible...
How can she move so fast?!
No! She's not her usual,
composed self at all!
I'll do whatever it takes to win!
Whatever it takes to live!
Mikasa found herself in
dire straits as well
when a mysterious Titan
appeared and attacked another Titan.
Unknown are the names
of the flowers that have been trampled
Birds have fallen to the earth
and long for the wind
Prayers won't solve anything
Only the will to fight
can change the here and now!
O pigs who laugh at the resolve
to walk over corpses to move forward
Livestock complacency? False prosperity?
Give us the freedom of dying,
starving wolves!
The humiliation of being caged
is what triggers us to fight back
We hunters slaughter prey
beyond the castle walls,
consumed with surging bloodlust,
as our crimson bows and arrows
pierce scarlet holes into the twilight
"I Can Hear His Heartbeat"
"The Struggle for Trost, Part 4"
There!
Your mobility gear still works,
and I've given you all my blades.
All I ask is that you
leave me with this one...
I'd rather not get
eaten alive, if I can help it.
N-No way...
Armin.
I'm not leaving you here.
B-But the place is swarming with Titans;
you can't possibly
carry someone while jumping--
Let's go!
No...
Please don't...
I'll only...
I'll only get more of my friends killed!
Wait!
Listen! I have a suggestion!
A suggestion?
Only you two can do it,
so I leave the choice to you...
I know it sounds crazy,
but could we use
that Titan to our advantage?
That Titan?!
It attacks other Titans and
doesn't show any interest in us.
So I'm wondering if we
could lead it to the supply building...
If it takes out the other Titans
for us, we just might all survive!
Lead it?! How do you
hope to lead that thing?!
My guess is it's fighting on instinct.
If you two take out the Titans around it,
it'll go and look for other Titans.
That'll naturally lead
it toward Headquarters.
W-We can't risk our
necks for some hopeful guess!
But if it works, we could eliminate
all the Titans attacking HQ
in one fell swoop!
--It seems worth trying.
--Huh?!
Are you serious?!
It's better to take a gamble than
wait for our inevitable deaths.
Let's go with Armin's suggestion.
You want us to
fight Titans with a Titan?!
Yes. I do.
If we fail, we'll be laughingstocks.
But if we succeed, everyone survives.
It all comes down to resolve.
All right! Fine!
Am I really cut out for this?
Am I really fit to have
a position of responsibility?
No!
No... now is the time.
Now is our chance, while the
Titans are preoccupied over there!
Now!
Make for HQ while we have the chance!
Now is our only chance!
If we run out of gas,
it's all over anyway!
Everyone, charge!
--Jean!
--Huh?
Thanks! You helped us get away!
Huh?!
It's all thanks to you!
It's like I said before!
You make a good leader!
I'm not so sure about that!
Damn!
How many made it?
How many comrades' deaths did I use?!
How many people
died because of my orders?
You're with the
supply team, aren't you?
Yeah...
Stop, Jean!
These are the ones who abandoned us!
People are dead because of you guys!
The Titans overran the supply room!
There was nothing we could do!
It's your job to deal with it anyway!
Hit the deck!
Crap...!
There are too many people!
--Hurry!
--Get further inside!
Stop! We can't all go at once!
Where'd Mikasa go?!
She ran out of gas!
She's long gone by now!
This is normal...
This must be what the real world is like...
Was I trying to
delude myself up until now?
Surely I knew what
the real world was like...
It's so obvious when you think about it...
There's no way we stand a
chance against these monstrosities...
What?!
Huh?
What the hell...?
Mikasa!
Man, that was close.
It's completely empty.
We did it! We managed to make it!
Wh-Whoa, you're alive!
--We did it, Armin!
--O-Ouch!
Your plan worked!
Guys!
That Titan's an Abnormal!
It's killin' all the other Titans!
And it has no interest in us!
We can use it to our
advantage to escape from here!
Use a Titan?!
A Titan, helping us?!
--What kind of nonsensical dream--
--It's no dream.
Whether it's an Abnormal
or not, I don't care.
We're going to let it rampage
here for as long as possible.
Because, realistically, that's our
best strategy for survival now.
It's okay.
That Titan's tougher than ordinary ones.
I doubt they'll take down this building
while that one's rampaging like crazy.
How much do you know about that Titan?
We can worry about that after we're safe.
Yeah. Let's survive first.
We found some!
They belong to the Military Police!
Damn things are all covered in dust...
Are you sure buckshot
is what we want to use?!
I mean, seriously...
Will guns even work against Titans?
They're far better than nothing, I feel.
If there are still seven Titans in the supply
room that are three or four meters tall,
this much firepower should be capable
of blinding them all simultaneously.
First, we'll use the lift to lower a
group of people from the center ceiling.
They'll then simultaneously fire
at the faces of each of the seven Titans,
thereby blinding them.
Then comes the moment of truth...
Seven people hiding up top
will strike the Titans'
vitals just after the guns fire.
In other words, this plan
will put everything on the line--
everyone's lives on the line--
for a single attack.
Seven people will have to slay seven
Titans at the same time in a single blow.
It'll be up to the seven most physically
fit and adept soldiers we have here.
So, umm, I'm sorry for placing
everyone's lives on your shoulders...
It's no problem.
If we fail, we die. The risk's
the same regardless of who goes.
Still, is this shabby idea of
mine really our best strategy?
We got no other choice.
We're out of time and options.
All we can do now is give it our all!
It'll be fine. Be confident.
You have a knack for
figuring out correct solutions.
Huh?
You even used it to save
my life and Eren's life before.
It did...? When?
The lift's ready!
The guns too! They're all loaded!
You just don't realize it.
--We can talk about it later.
--Yeah.
Still, can we really take out all
the Titans without our ODM gear?
Of course we can!
These Titans are only three or four meters tall.
Targeting their vitals will be a cinch.
Yeah.
Regardless of size, their vitals go
from the head to the nape of the neck...
...one meter high and ten centimeters across!
You can also shove
one of these up their asses!
Those are their only two weak spots!
I never knew about that one!
This is the first I've heard of it, too.
Reiner.
Those could end up
being your last words, you know.
Good. Their numbers haven't increased.
Proceeding with operation!
Stay clam! We need
to lure them all the way in!
Steady...
Avoid a disadvantageous fight...
If you don't want anyone to die...
...then make this attack count!
Steady...
Ready...
Fire!
I got mine!
How about you guys?!
U-Umm...
--I'm sorry for suddenly sneaking up and...
--C-Crap...
I'm very sorry...!
Sasha and Conny!
Hurry! Lend them backup!
I'm... umm...
I'm very sorry!
Mikasa!
You saved me!
Are you all right?
Thanks to you!
Then get up.
I owe you one...
No problem.
Oh, man.
That was a close call, Annie.
I'm really glad you didn't end up hurt.
They've all been slain!
Switch to resupply work!
We did it!
--All right! We're gonna survive!
--And no more Titans are coming inside!
All thanks to that
berserk Titan out there!
I caved in to that Titan...
I'm too ashamed to face the others...!
There'll be plenty of
time to sneer at you later!
For now, we gotta escape!
I can't see myself as much of a leader.
Don't talk like that anymore.
I don't mean any offense by this,
but I think the fact you aren't strong
really lets you understand
how the weak feel.
And your skill at recognizing
a situation as it unfolds
gives you a clear grasp of what
needs to be done now, you know?
You made the right call.
It's what got me moving.
It's why I'm alive now.
Everyone ready?! It's time to scram!
--Let's move!
--Scale the wall!
Rendezvous with the main forces!
Mikasa?!
Mikasa!
We have to get out of here!
That Titan...
They're cannibalizing it?!
I guess it can't regenerate its body?
I thought that if we could somehow
figure out what's up with that Titan,
it could've helped us break
free from this hopeless situation...
I agree.
We'll learn nothing at all
if it ends up getting eaten!
For now, we have to get
rid of the ones clinging to it
and help keep it alive!
Are you insane, Reiner?!
We can finally get our asses out of here!
And what if there's a chance
that Titan could become our ally?
It'd be a more powerful weapon
than any cannon, wouldn't you agree?
Ally...?
Are you actually serious?!
That one...!
That's the Abnormal that ate Thomas!
Oh, man...
What was it you wanted to save again?
Looks like it's finished for good.
All right, that's enough! Let's get going!
As if that monster would ever be our ally...
A Titan's a Titan.
What's with you guys?
Mikasa!
It's Eren...
His severed arm and leg are back...
He'd been swallowed by a Titan back then...
Back then...
How is this possible?
Does this mean Eren did all this...?
Your dreams are where your heart is
They're more fragile than life itself
Over and over you cast them aside,
only to find more
Now, rest in peace
Pounding impulses defile the things we wish for
and the more we forget
the more we remember again
In this beautiful, cruel world
all I can do is ask why we're still alive
Oh, with our strength--and our weakness--
what are we going to protect if there's no sense
to anything anymore?
"I'm going to drive out the Titans."
That strong emotion
transformed Eren into a Titan.
However, the Garrison Regiment
deems him a threat to humanity
and turns its swords at him.
"Whereabouts of His Left Arm"
"The Struggle for Trost, Part 5"